okay okay
[Music]
so please check your cell phone Geshe
Michael releasing sitting on a pile so
cellular is
then pull in your stomach
slightly method from legal fermenting
and keep it there
today in her yoga class Aaron talked
about vacuum the air annoy into classic
yoga blow acerca the refectory Aspira
Dora they were sealed for your shoulders
back little bit here to Sun rose and set
resumed poco check your eyelids are they
soft not tense observe a annalisa
vakidis and purposes 10 Rella hollows
and are your fingers relaxed it's done
to the little house we're gonna do 10
verse 10 very slow breaths vamos I said
the air respiration is muy profundis
lentils or maybe a few more he saw some
Pokemon and I'd like you to try a new
way of reading your content and una
nueva manera there respira so imagine
you are breathing out of your forehead
guru Cosima Keenan just and raspy rondo
also friending you are breathing out and
in three or four whisper and what
resident respectful in a land or excel
on the lower part of your forehead
almost between your eyebrows and even
through sick let's try pretend that the
breath is coming in and out there and
we'll take you 10 12 15 breaths in
Mahina fing heck
Lisa Lisa que la espera 16 Alice its
Alice poor Ellen Tracy ho llevamos
estado c'est un poco Maris Bellagio
knees
and I'd like you to bring your mind to
this morning aura one potentially
concentration in lo que paso esta mañana
and try to find the one thing you did
what you think is most good karma this
morning intenta pensar en contrar ever
qualify el mejor poincaré Madison brás
de esta mañana lo mejor Kasich is the
Perl in masses Dominion
so check you know your morning try to
remember your morning you will have a
few choices and choose the the one thing
you did which was the barest yeah what
the record Arturo kissed in the manana
it Andrews various once acciones
the las cuales allah he really here like
Islamic fourth
now in the middle of the game what was
the the best thing that you did the best
karma hora piensa el mediodía durante el
mediodía call for mejor karma case in
Brazil and for Iraqis East
and then just before this class in a few
hours before this class what was the
best thing you did he supported towards
the school ultimate dos tres horas antes
de la clase give a llama forty system
now the second law of karma la segunda
label Karma
it says time each of those seeds Lisa
get cada una de sus familias karmic ask
a sandblasting those three cutsies this
is tres amigas param Akash bespoke
Easton Tomatoes yon they were
multiplying thousands of times before
they open say multiply Quran Miele
services until the average cell Florence
air they will create major events in
your life in the future you know the
future of Iraq and Iran event those
Granby CMAs maybe next month maybe in
six months
kisses help Roxy mommy's kisses and
sighs messes so now I'd like you to go
we'll go again through the day
ora vamos a volver serán record reading
a memorial LDN we'll go again through
those three good days aura volvo demo so
visually solace record Arliss and try to
imagine how they might be when they
finished multiplying Trotter imagine art
a la experiencia total external turna
Quan determinant multiplicative Randy
Florez con so please use your
imagination don't be shy not just in yo
e not a thing as an El Oso that
imaginación in fantasy a Buddha said the
seeds were multiplied a thousand
sometimes Buddha copious Amyas paramitas
say multiply quran mila services so
using your imagination and with a lot of
joy try to imagine what beautiful thing
could happen in six months from the sea
whip Elizondo party - yon he was an
eleven disfrutan de mucho intent imagine
Arturo and says messes
give us who say they're con esto Samia
como te papa sorry
so let's go back to the morning vamos a
Loki system de mañana try to remember
that good seed you planted intend to
record our is awareness amigas in Grozny
and imagine in a few months in máquina
de unos meses it just multiplies many
thousands of times si esta su Malika
Mila services what kind of experience
will come to you to experiencia vendrá
team be creative
Musa to create TV dad relax the manera
real aha have fun here today let your
imagination exaggerated something really
big parameter ticket as her own also I
was so - Martinez Yan is already mention
poke another noise no just a minute okay
here we go
misawa's the end comic result of the
cutting you did this morning multiplied
dozens of times
vas imagine arte el resultado karmic Oh
finally el fruto de la vall completo de
las semillas karma Cassandra's delvia
now please move your mind to the middle
of the day or forgotten in love wine / -
Amelia case in Brazil even Dalian mass
the mediodía think about the best karma
uted in the middle of today
bien sur la mejor ayuda
Jeff resist Aryan mass media and then
multiply thousands of times more deeply
the same - a película Milla services and
try to imagine what's going to come to
you in within the next few months intent
imagine a more Flores air and naciente
spaces
now please think of the good karma you
did in the last few hours
bien sûr and I went over and when accion
karma cactus is dead as a poker mr.
salty Mosasaurus and please let your
imagination copy don't don't give it
small let me take my machine accion
sagar and assess that Canyon
Canelo so to imaginación and try to
imagine a happiness which is much more
than you feel notice didn't imagine
earth the Munna felicidad mucho my your
delicates thus experiment under those
years in the next few months when this
karma opens neuroscientist menses pond
was the Sameach Erika Flores gun after
it grows it was ever crazy okay here we
go
now please come back to your breath well
where the respiration three long exhales
classic Salah Sione's largas and offered
this good karma to other people
yes una friend in beyond west wing karma
otras personas
and slowly open your eyes will enter
meant every row suppose take a stretch
yes dear
[Applause]